<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BackstoryInjections>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>SpacePirate69</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Space pirate</Title>
    <TitleShort>Pirate</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>Piracy appears everywhere that governments are weak and society spread thin. NAME was part of this age-old part of human existence, extorting and smashing peaceful trade ships for profit.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>PitBrawler20</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Pit brawler</Title>
    <TitleShort>Brawler</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>NAME was nine years old when HE got in HIS first fight. HECAP won, but more important was the enjoyment of HIS audience. Pit fighting turned out to be a lucrative career for those who could survive it. And it was even mostly legal.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>IllegalShipwright28</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Illegal shipwright</Title>
    <TitleShort>Shipwright</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>There is a law that says that you're not allowed to put terawatt-range grasers on a cargo scow. Especially if you hide them under what looks like a communications dish for better ambush potential. NAME discovered that there is great profit to be made, however, from those who are uninterested in these laws.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>Courtesean56</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Courtesean</Title>
    <TitleShort>Courtesean</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>NAME was used for HIS body by hundreds of customers in brothels on several planets. HECAP gained some mental marks and a special kind of street smarts.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>SpaceMarine10</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Space marine</Title>
    <TitleShort>Marine</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>NAME was a warrior in an Imperial navy. HISCAP job was to punch into enemy starships, gun down the crew, and capture the ship intact. And HE was good at it.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

  <RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>
    <defName>Assassin35</defName>
    <Slot>Adulthood</Slot>
    <Title>Assassin</Title>
    <TitleShort>Assassin</TitleShort>
    <BaseDesc>NAME was a professional assassin. HECAP was cold, calculating, and made a good profit. In this business, an utter lack of empathy was an asset.</BaseDesc>
  </RimTrans.Framework.Injection.BackstoryInjection>

</BackstoryInjections>